Here we go, a programme that takes you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We'll be bringing you behind-the-scenes footage of our recordings and rehearsals.
We'll start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs, their recording sessions, rehearsals and other production processes.
Well then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I'm Okamura, and I'm talking about the Hello Project concert that 3 of us performed at the end of the concert the other day.
At the rehearsal, I really felt Beyond-san's, what can I say?
I thought that Beyond's motivation, or rather their seriousness and enthusiasm, was wonderful,
I thought it was really cool to see them dancing and performing at 100% from the rehearsal,
The spring tour is scheduled to take place next,
This will be the first tour with 13 members.
I'm sure there will be a lot of changes.
I'm sure there will be a lot of changes and we, Morningless's Poofer
I want to do my best to show you something wonderful.
I want to do my best so that we can create something wonderful.
This tour has made me realize that.
That's really nice.
Thank you very much.
I'm Saito.
I'm going to talk about 3 of us.
Project concert in January. Project concert in January.
Project concert in January, we performed the song "Fate Cha Cha Cha Chan" as the first song.
I performed the song "Fate Cha Cha Cha Chan" as the first song.
From the Tachikawa concert in February
Chacha Sing 2024 Ochanoma version was changed.
In fact, the Chacha Sing Ochanoma version has a different choreography
The choreography was also changed.
It was originally a song by Berryz KOBO.
so there are some parts that have been rearranged and changed a bit.
I wondered if the fans of Angstrom and JuiceJuice would dance along with us.
But when the song started, everyone did the same choreography from the beginning and I was so happy.
I'm really impressed by the fans' ability to adapt to the situation.
I haven't seen the new TV show "Tea Mama" yet.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder if I'll be able to see it in Iraq.
I'll be happy if I can see it.
Let's start with this letter.
Tsubaki Factory new member lesson video
The lessons of the 3 years who joined as new members of Tsubaki Factory have started!
Please have a look!
Today we're really going to do the basics of the basics.
I might stop the sound normally...
Well, that's each to their own.
I hope you'll learn how to use everyone's crap.
Today we're only going to do the real, real basics.
If you used to be a dancer...
I don't want to be celebrated.
There might be a little bit of a difference between the two.
That's why we're all going to group together.
You can't just say, "I can do it from the basics.
I can do it from the basics.
Okay.
Let's have fun.
Okay, now I'm going to push down on your left ear with my right hand, and then I'm going to push my hand down so that my shoulder doesn't come up.
Push the hand down so the shoulder doesn't come up.
Pull your hand down so your shoulder doesn't come up.
Go firmly through the front, imaging your awareness, cherish it.
Now, from left to left, go through the back of the left side.
Keep going through on the opposite, back side.
It should be pretty much up.
I'm going to go to the front.
Let's stretch, let's stretch.
It doesn't come up like this normally.
This butt...
I've been on my toes for a while now.
It's coming up from your stomach, so don't lower it from where it is now.
It comes up from the place where you lower it.
There's no here.
Your shoulders are very free right now.
So, go here.
We'll do that last one.
Tighten your hips.
Spread your stomach.
Just relax.
OK, spread out, use the relax-swave, and you can move anywhere you want.
Turn around. Opposite.
Use the wave. Opposite.
One, two, three, four.
Let's take it backwards.
Five, six, let's go opposite.
And that's the end of the kick-ass lesson.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
I've been doing jazz for a long time.
I've only recently started hip-hop.
It's hard for me to get over my jazz habit.
I've only just learned the basics of hip-hop, so it's hard to develop my jazz habits, and it was very difficult to get the basic rhythm of hip-hop.
It was very difficult for me to get the basic rhythm of hip-hop.
I do muscle training every day.
I should improve my training a bit more.
I thought I should improve my training a bit more.
Muscle training, flexibility and rhythm
It's all very difficult.
It was really tough.
To be honest, today's lesson
But I'll work on it more from now on.
I'm going to work harder and get the rhythm right.
I'll try to get the rhythm right.
I'm going to work on my flexibility.
to get my stomach on the floor.
I also want to work on my muscle training
I also want to work harder at muscle training so that I can do it faster.
I'm doing some dancing, and I want to work on getting it on when I'm going down, and I want to work on my strength training too, so that I can do it faster.
I'm doing some dancing, and when I'm going down, I'll do a forward step like this, and then I'll take a step forward and then I'll do a backward step.
I'd like to add a song that makes the bullet fall straight down again today.
I'd like to do push-ups, sit-ups and flexibility.
I'd like to work hard on push-ups, sit-ups and flexibility.
When I first joined the group, I had a basic lesson, but I was really nervous and wondered what I was going to do and what I would do if the teacher got angry with me.
I was a bit scared, and the three of us could see the scared looks on our faces.
But when I was leaving, I met the three of them and they seemed to be getting on really well together.
I was cheering them on and thinking, "Good luck, we're about to start lessons.
I was cheering them on, but when you start working, you don't do the basics.
I think you can't just go on and on learning songs and songs.
So I think you're going to have to work hard to solidify the basics while you can, and I hope you'll continue to work hard in the future.
I hope they'll continue to do their best in the future.
I've said hello to each of the three Tsubaki Facto d members, but we haven't had the chance to get to know each other yet.
But we haven't been able to get to know each other yet.
I kept saying how cute and lovely they were when I saw them working hard in their basic lessons.
I think that all three of them are very ordinary people, so I think there are still many things we don't know about them.
I'm sure there are still many things we don't understand.
But I think they will bring a new wind to Hello Project.
I'm really looking forward to it.
We'll continue to bring you updates on the new members' lessons here on Atsushi, so please look forward to it.
Please look forward to it!
That's all for now, here's a video of the new Tsubaki Factory member's lesson. I'm sure something good will come out of it.
Beyonce Maeda Shin's hair arrangement
This is a hair arrangement by Shin Maeda of Beyoncé.
Now let's see what it's all about this time.
Let's have a look.
I'm Shin Maeda of Beyons Amano no Mori Kami.
Today I'd like to introduce the way I usually do my hair.
Yes, I've been cutting my hair short again since the beginning of this year.
Last year I wore it long for about a year, but
Now I have a short cut again.
I'd like to introduce short haircuts to you all.
I'll start right away.
Usually when I wake up in the morning, I have a lot of sleeping habits when I have a short haircut.
My hair bounces around here and there.
And while I'm sleeping, it probably goes up like this.
So I often end up with a lot of fluff around here.
So I start by wetting and drying my hair.
Today it's surprisingly calm.
I'd like to continue like this.
I've always had straight hair that tends to be flat.
I want to give it a bit of volume here.
And since I have a precipitous cliff, I'm going to add volume in the back.
I'm going to do it softly.
I think it would be better to part my hair like this, but I don't usually do it like this.
I don't usually do it like that.
I'll do it as usual.
I iron the whole hair like this.
The ends of the hair should be tucked in a little bit.
There are short hair, short hair, long hair and long hair.
And if the collar is long or short
I want to see short hair become more and more popular.
I wish short hair would become more popular.
The back of the hair is a key point for me.
I iron from the roots upwards.
I've also had my collar cut short, but just a little bit.
Run the iron through.
Lightly. When you look at it from the side...
I think it looks better if it's rounded here.
It's more rounded.
I usually wear it over my ears.
I'd like to show you a version with the hair down.
Then I'll show you a version with the hair inside here.
Let's try it.
This tier is really cute.
I recommend this cut.
Oh, and the fringes. I'll iron the middle part.
When I ask my stylist to cut my hair, I want the lines here to be really clean, but I went to the salon yesterday and learned a few things.
I went to a hairdresser yesterday and learned a few things, so I'll share them with you.
Take a thin, thin strand and iron it vertically.
Iron vertically.
And iron it outwards like this.
If you iron it outwards, you'll get a nice line here.
But...
Maybe I haven't trained enough.
It's important from here.
I'm going to put balm on it.
I don't know how much to say.
Blend it into your hands.
Start at the collar.
I'm going to apply it mainly to the ends of your hair.
I don't want it to look sticky.
Let's apply it like this to the fringe too.
And then apply the rest of it to the bangs.
Apply to the outside like this.
I sometimes apply too much at this point.
It's okay to just let it happen on those days.
Fine-tuning is important with these fringes.
I'll keep adjusting them until I'm happy with them.
This is probably the most time-consuming part.
That's good.
Just when you think you've got it right.
Spray.
When we go live, of course.
I've got to make sure it's really tight.
But when I go out on a regular day...
I'm fine.
I've been spraying a lot.
I don't know...
My hair is very light.
I get blown away by the wind just walking around.
I usually try to harden it.
Spray the roots first.
Be careful not to let the wind blow it away at this point.
Give it a quick spritz all over.
And here.
Here's where I apply the all-important blow-dryer.
Be careful with the volume.
Like this.
I usually wear my hair down like this, but...
I usually wear my hair down like this, but I often wear it over my ears.
I'll give it a try.
I'm going to try it with the ears up.
Like this.
It also looks really neat.
I highly recommend it because it gives you a beautiful silhouette.
And if you take out a bit of hair from here to here at the fringe
Just a little bit of hair here and there can make a big difference.
You can adjust the amount of hair here and there.
I love the hair here at this point.
And I think it's cute even if you let it down a little bit more.
I think it's cute even if it's like this.
It's like this.
It's finished.
How do you like it?
My point is to use a hair dryer after spraying.
I think this is better than just spraying.
I think it's less likely to fall apart if you add a hairdryer to the spray.
If you want to keep your hair from falling apart, I recommend you try it.
I also think the key is the way you cut it,
I think the key is to make a rounded shape.
I would be very happy if you could try to imitate me.
That's all for now, this is Shin Maeda from Beyoncé Amamorigawa Bi.
Thank you for watching.
When I saw the VTR, I was reminded once again that Maeda-san looks good in any hairstyle.
She was so cute when she had long hair.
The short cut she has now can only be done by someone who looks really good with it.
That's really true.
When I was a student, before I joined Hello Project.
There was a time when I had a short cut.
I wish I had come across this video back then.
So if there is a time to have a short cut in the future.
I'd like to set it like Maeda-san's.
I really want to set my hair like Maeda-san's. Maeda-san has such a beautiful face and I love her short hair, so I'm really grateful to her for giving me another short cut.
I love Maeda-san, so personally I'm really grateful to her for giving me a short cut again, but I've always had long hair and I'm good at arranging it, but I just can't do it myself.
I'm good at arranging other people's hair, but I just can't do mine.
I'm good at arranging other people's hair, but I just can't do my own.
It makes all the difference.
I want to do my best so that I can do mine in the future.
That's all for now, this is Beyonce Maeda Shin's hair arrangement.
You can do it!
Morning Musume。24's Homare Okamura and
and Madoka Saito from Ocha no Oma.
Next up.
Morning Musume。23
Wake up call When you wake up
Yumeshita Tatko vocal recording
All right, let's start filming then.
We'll film in blocks, starting with the A melody.
I'll give it a go.
Take one.
We're going to shoot in blocks, so I'll try it once. Please.
Yes, yes, that's what I mean.
So, now the next one, the head, now.
The head is moving, right? Fixed here. Then move the other part and do the same thing.
I'm not here for you to push your femininity on each other.
That's all I'm saying.
Oh, it works.
Yeah, it's good. It's like that.
Let's continue.
Unfortunately, it's not for you.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Be cute.
Be cool.
Mocking.
Weird.
Creatures with masks. We have to accept every face.
Maybe "cute" is a bit long.
Cute, cool, mocking, suspicious...
Let's stop with "cute, cool, mawkish, and suspicious.
The rest is fine.
Oh, I have to affirm, but I'm stretching it, so I have to affirm, but I'm stretching it.
I have to affirm.
Let's stop with "I have to affirm...".
A multifaceted creature, any face is okay if you don't affirm it.
Let's try the B melody.
I want to get into the chorus.
Dark Nine, let's sing it all the way to "Wake Up".
Okay.
A multifaceted creature, we have to affirm every face.
It's surely boring to leave it to others
I'll decide for myself... and I can't shake this feeling.
I don't want to deceive myself
Wake up call
Let's stop once and for all and leave it to others.
That's where we're connected now.
I'm sure it's boring to leave it to others
I'll decide for myself, I can't shake this feeling
Let's stop right there.
And finally, more... I'm not fully up yet, so I'm sure I can go higher.
You can go all out.
A multifaceted creature, I don't approve of any face.
I'm sure it's boring to leave it up to others. I'll decide for myself, I can't shake this feeling.
I don't want to deceive you.
Wake up call
OK.
Shall we continue?
Everyone has colourful possibilities
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to change your clothes
I'll be reborn again and again JUST WE JUST WE JUST WE JUST WE JUST WE JUST WE
Please let me make fun of you DANCE BABY DANCE BABY DANCE BABY DANCE BABY DANCE BABY
Dance baby Dance baby Dance baby
Now that was good, wasn't it?
Just now.
I sang "Just" at the beginning.
It was kind of cool.
Let's go all the way with that.
Everyone has colourful possibilities.
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to change your clothes
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it OK!
I'll take the part you left out then.
That's too close.
I'll just take the heart of someone who sings Kusubu.
More, get the rhythm right, because it's flowing now.
Kusubu uta somebody's heart
I'll sing it.
Yes.
OK.
Let's try the next one.
Okay.
Then let's rap next.
Yes! I'll stretch the end and the lution a bit. Same as before.
And the dance is a bit deejay-ish. Stretch it out a bit at the end.
Future forward! Evolution today! Smiles and energy! Revolution of love! Live cheering, congrats!
Let's dance! Dance danceas deas deas deas!
Yeah, let's just take the first line.
Future forward! Evolution today!
Smiles and energy!
OK! OK, we're done then!
Yes, thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, this song Wake Up Call is the first song for the J Miki members.
It's the first song for the J Miki members.
It was a time when Mizuki-san was still a member of the group.
We've already sung it quite a lot now.
I think we've all been singing it for quite a while now and it's starting to sink in.
I was really nervous about it.
There were a lot of things I couldn't do at first, and I started to look more and more gloomy,
I know how you feel, but the number of takes shows that you really worked hard, and I'm sure there will be more difficulties in the future, especially with the rhythm and mornings.
I'm sure there will be times when you will lose heart, but I want you to continue to sing happily.
I want you to continue to sing and do your best.
When I saw all of Ako-chan's recordings like this, I could hear her young, mature voice.
I thought she had a young, mature voice.
As she continues to grow and develop, I wonder how her voice will evolve.
I'm also looking forward to seeing how her voice will evolve as she continues to grow.
I also saw the video of Haruka Inoue, a member of the 17th term.
I think there was a video of Haruka Inoue, a member of the 17th term, recording.
Both of them are good singers but their voices are different.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how the two 17th term members will perform in the future.
That's all for Morning Musume。 23 Wake Up Call: When You Wake Up was the vocal recording of Ako Yumiga.
Don't be too hard on yourself, take care of yourself!
It's time to say goodbye to Okamura Homare and Saito Madoka's up-cam!
We've seen a lot of footage this time.
I, Saito, when I saw the lessons of the three main members of Ritsuki Factory...
I can't explain it, but it brought back memories of when I first joined the Halo Pro trainees.
I also remembered my first recording sessions with Ako-chan Yumigita and myself.
I also remembered my first recording session with Ako-chan Yumigita, and I also remembered my first recording session with Ko-chan.
I remember the time when I was a new member, and I also remember the time when I was with Madoka-chan, and I thought I'll never forget that picture and I'll keep working hard.
I also learned a lot from Shin Maeda's hair arrangement. I know it's not important to talk about the volume of the hair, but sometimes it gets a bit sticky, so I learned a lot about how to iron it like that, and it was a lot of fun. It was a lot of fun.
In APKAMI, we go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT Group.
We'll be introducing you to parts you don't normally get to see, so please subscribe to our channel. This time, our upcami partners were Morning Musume. 24's Okamura Honour and Ocha no Ma's Saito Ma Taka!
Goodbye.
Next time on Upokami.
The recording of Angulum Red Line
And
Tsubaki Factory's latest album
The recording of Third Forment will be released!
Please look forward to it!